Local 1199 Records 5510
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Jewish Memorial Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Jewish Memorial Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Jewish Memorial Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- John F. Kennedy Hospital, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- John T. Mather Memorial Hospital, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Joint Diseases Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1968 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Joint Diseases Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1959-1968 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Joint Diseases Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1959-1968 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Kessler Institute, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Kings Brook Hospital, 1969-1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Kleen-Rite, 1969-1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Knickerbocker Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Knickerbocker Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Knickerbocker Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Knickerbocker Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Lakeside Hospital, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Laura Parker Nursing Home, 1965-1970 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Laura Parker Nursing Home, 1965-1970 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Laurelview Nursing Homes, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Lawrence Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Lawrence Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Lemberger Home [folder 1 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Lemberger Home [folder 2 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Lemberger Home [folder 3 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Lemberger Home [folder 4 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Lenox Hill Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Lenox Hill Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Lenox Hill Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Lenox Hill Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Lincoln Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Lincoln Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Long Beach Memorial Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Long Beach Memorial Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Long Hill, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Long Island College Hospital, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Long Island Doctor's Hospital [folder 1 of 5], 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Long Island Doctor's Hospital [folder 2 of 5], 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Long Island Doctor's Hospital [folder 3 of 5], 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Long Island Doctor's Hospital [folder 4 of 5], 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Long Island Doctor's Hospital [folder 5 of 5], 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital [folder 1 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital [folder 2 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital [folder 3 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital [folder 4 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital [folder 5 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Lutheran Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Lutheran Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Lutheran Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Lutheran Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Lutheran Medical Center [folder 1 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Lutheran Medical Center [folder 2 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Lutheran Medical Center [folder 3 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Lutheran Medical Center [folder 4 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Maimonides Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1957-1971 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Maimonides Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1957-1971 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Maimonides Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1957-1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Maimonides Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1957-1971 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Manhasset Medical Center [folder 1 of 4], 1960-1971 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Manhasset Medical Center [folder 2 of 4], 1960-1971 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Manhasset Medical Center [folder 3 of 4], 1960-1971 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Manhasset Medical Center [folder 4 of 4], 1960-1971 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Manhattan Eye and Ear Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Manhattan Eye and Ear Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Manhattan Eye and Ear Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Manhattan Eye and Ear Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Manhattan General Hospital, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Maple Lawn Convalescent Home, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Martin Luther King Health Center, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Mary Manning Walsh Nursing Home, 1969-1971 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Memorial Center for Women, 1968-1971 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Memorial Hospital, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Menorah Home and Hospital, 1959-1963 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Mercer Hospital, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Methodist Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1968 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Methodist Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1968 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Misericordia-Fordham Hospital, 1963-1965 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Modern Maintenance, 1967-1971 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Montclair Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Montclair Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Montclair Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Montefiore Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1958-1971 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Montefiore Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1958-1971 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Montefiore Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1958-1971 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Montefiore Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1958-1971 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Morrisania Hospital, 1960-1971 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Mt. Morris Park Hospital, 1959-1960 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 1 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 2 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 3 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 4 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 5 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Mount Vernon Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1969 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Mount Vernon Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1969 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Mountainside Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1960-1967 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Mountainside Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1960-1967 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Mountainside Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1960-1967 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Nassau Hospital, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- National Dietetics [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- National Dietetics [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Neustadter Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1971 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Neustadter Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1971 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- New Haven Convalescent, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- New Jersey Medical Center, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- New Rochelle Hospital, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- New York Cardiac Canter, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- New York Convalescent Home, 1968-1971 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- New York Eye and Ear Hospital, 1959-1963 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- New York Infirmary [folder 1 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- New York Infirmary [folder 2 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- New York Infirmary [folder 3 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- New York Infirmary [folder 4 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- New York Hospital, 1959-1963 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- New York University Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- New York University Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- New York University Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Newark Beth Israel Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1971 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Newark Beth Israel Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1971 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Newark City Hospital, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Newark Gardens Sanitarium [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1968 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Newark Gardens Sanitarium [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1968 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Newark Gardens Sanitarium [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1968 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Noah Nursing Home, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- North Shore, 1965-1966 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Northfield Manor Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Northfield Manor Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Northfield Manor Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Northfield Nursing Home, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Old Men and Aged Couples Home, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Orange Memorial Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Orange Memorial Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Orange Memorial Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Orange Memorial Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1964-1971 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Overlook Hospital, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Park City Hospital, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Parkchester, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Parkview Hospital, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Parkway Hospital, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Parkway Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Parkway Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Parkway Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Passaic General Hospital, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Pelham Bay General Hospital, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Peninsula General Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Peninsula General Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Peninsula General Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Peninsula General Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Perth Amboy General Hospital, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Pine Acres Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Pine Acres Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Pine Acres Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Pine Haven, 1965-1967 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Polyclinic Hospital, 1959-1963 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Pompton Lakes Nursing Home, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Pond Point Convalescent Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Pond Point Convalescent Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Presbyterian Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1966 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Presbyterian Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1966 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Prospect Gardens, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Prospect Heights Hospital, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Queens Memorial Hospital (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Ramapo Manor Nursing Home [folder 1 of 5], 1964-1970 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Ramapo Manor Nursing Home [folder 2 of 5], 1964-1970 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Ramapo Manor Nursing Home [folder 3 of 5], 1964-1970 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Ramapo Manor Nursing Home [folder 4 of 5], 1964-1970 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Ramapo Manor Nursing Home [folder 5 of 5], 1964-1970 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Richmond Cleaners [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Richmond Cleaners [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Richmond Memorial Hospital, 1964-1970 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Riverdale Hebrew Home, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Riverview Hospital, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Rockefeller Institute, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Rockville Nursing Center, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Rofay Nursing Home, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Roosevelt Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1967 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Roosevelt Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1959-1967 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Roosevelt Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1959-1967 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Ross Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Ross Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Ross Sanitarium [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1967 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Ross Sanitarium [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1967 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Saddle Brook Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Saddle Brook Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Saddle Brook Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- St. Barnabas Hospital [folder 1 of 7], 1962-1971 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- St. Barnabas Hospital [folder 2 of 7], 1962-1971 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- St. Barnabas Hospital [folder 3 of 7], 1962-1971 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- St. Barnabas Hospital [folder 4 of 7], 1962-1971 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- St. Barnabas Hospital [folder 5 of 7], 1962-1971 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- St. Barnabas Hospital [folder 6 of 7], 1962-1971 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- St. Barnabas Hospital [folder 7 of 7], 1962-1971 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- St. Clare's Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1962-1966 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- St. Clare's Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1966 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- St. Frances Hospital, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- St. James Hospital, 1964-1968 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- St. John's Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- St. John's Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- St. John's Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- St. John's Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- St. John's Hospital (Queens) [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1971 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- St. John's Hospital (Queens) [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1971 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- St. John's Smithtown Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1968 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- St. John's Smithtown Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1968 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- St. Luke's Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1968 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- St. Luke's Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1959-1968 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- St. Luke's Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1959-1968 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- St. Mary's Hospital [folder 1 of 6], 1963-1971 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- St. Mary's Hospital [folder 2 of 6], 1963-1971 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- St. Mary's Hospital [folder 3 of 6], 1963-1971 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- St. Mary's Hospital [folder 4 of 6], 1963-1971 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- St. Mary's Hospital [folder 5 of 6], 1963-1971 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- St. Mary's Hospital [folder 6 of 6], 1963-1971 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- St. Michael's Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- St. Michael's Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- St. Patrick Home, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- St. Patrick's Hospital, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- St. Peter's Hospital, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- St. Vincent's Hospital, 1963-1968 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Samaritan Hospital, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Saw Mill River Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1971 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Saw Mill River Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1971 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Sayville Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Sayville Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Sayville Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Schrafft's Food, 1967-1971 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Seagirt Home of Old Israel, 1969-1971 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Seagirt Village Hospital, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Seaside Convalescent Home, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Sephardic Home for the Aged [folder 1 of 4], 1960-1971 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Sephardic Home for the Aged [folder 2 of 4], 1960-1971 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Sephardic Home for the Aged [folder 3 of 4], 1960-1971 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Sephardic Home for the Aged [folder 4 of 4], 1960-1971 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Shore Memorial Hospital, 1965-1966 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Smithtown Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1964-1971 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Smithtown Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1964-1971 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Smithtown Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1964-1971 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Sons and Daughters of Israel, 1961-1963 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- South Nassau Community Hospital, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Southampton Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Southampton Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Southampton Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1971 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Southside Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1964-1971 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Southside Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1964-1971 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Southside Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1964-1971 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Staten Island Hospital, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Stonybrook Hospital, 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Stratford Connecticut Hospital, 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Syosset Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1964-1971 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Syosset Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1964-1971 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Syosset Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1964-1971 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Teaneck Nursing Home, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Temco Medical Center, 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Terminal Cleaners, 1967-1969 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Todd Nursing Home, 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Trafalgar Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1971 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Trafalgar Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1959-1971 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Trafalgar Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1959-1971 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Union Hospital, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- United Hebrew Home for the Aged, 1967-1971 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- United Odd Fellows Home, 1966-1971 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Unity Hospital [folder 1 of 5], 1960-1971 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Unity Hospital [folder 2 of 5], 1960-1971 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Unity Hospital [folder 3 of 5], 1960-1971 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Unity Hospital [folder 4 of 5], 1960-1971 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Unity Hospital [folder 5 of 5], 1960-1971 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- University Hospital, 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Weathersfield Manor, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- West Haven Manor, 1968-1971 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- West Hudson Hospital, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Westhampton [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Westhampton [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Westhampton [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Westport Manor, 1968-1970 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- White Plains Hospital, 1968-1971 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Women's of St. Lukes, 1963-1965 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Woodbury Nursing Home, 1967-1971 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Woodland's Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1971 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Woodland's Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1971 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Workmen's Circle [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Workmen's Circle [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Workmen's Circle [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Wyckoff Heights Hospital, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Wyndover Convalescent Home, 1969-1971 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Yeshiva University Hospital, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Yonkers General Hospital, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Yonkers Professional Hospital, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Bronx Area Membership Meetings [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Bronx Area Membership Meetings [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Bronx Area Membership Meetings [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn Area Membership Meetings [folder 1 of 5], 1964-1972 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn Area Membership Meetings [folder 2 of 5], 1964-1972 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn Area Membership Meetings [folder 3 of 5], 1964-1972 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Brooklyn Area Membership Meetings [folder 4 of 5], 1964-1972 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Brooklyn Area Membership Meetings [folder 5 of 5], 1964-1972 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Connecticut Area Membership Meetings [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Connecticut Area Membership Meetings [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1971 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Downtown Area Membership Meetings [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1967 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Downtown Area Membership Meetings [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1967 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- New Jersey Area Membership Meetings [folder 1 of 6], 1965-1968 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- New Jersey Area Membership Meetings [folder 2 of 6], 1965-1968 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- New Jersey Area Membership Meetings [folder 3 of 6], 1965-1968 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- New Jersey Area Membership Meetings [folder 4 of 6], 1965-1968 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- New Jersey Area Membership Meetings [folder 5 of 6], 1965-1968 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- New Jersey Area Membership Meetings [folder 6 of 6], 1965-1968 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Queens Area Membership Meetings [folder 1 of 4], 1966-1971 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Queens Area Membership Meetings [folder 2 of 4], 1966-1971 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Queens Area Membership Meetings [folder 3 of 4], 1966-1971 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Queens Area Membership Meetings [folder 4 of 4], 1966-1971 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Uptown Area Membership Meetings [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Uptown Area Membership Meetings [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Uptown Area Membership Meetings [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Hospital Tally Sheets [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1962 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Hospital Tally Sheets [folder 2 of 3], 1959-1962 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Hospital Tally Sheets [folder 3 of 3], 1959-1962 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Leaflet Distribution, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Organizing General [folder 1 of 8], 1959-1971 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Organizing General [folder 2 of 8], 1959-1971 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Organizing General [folder 3 of 8], 1959-1971 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Organizing General [folder 4 of 8], 1959-1971 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Organizing General [folder 5 of 8], 1959-1971 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Organizing General [folder 6 of 8], 1959-1971 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Organizing General [folder 7 of 8], 1959-1971 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Organizing General [folder 8 of 8], 1959-1971 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Organizing General -(Rates, Increments, etc.), 1958-1962 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Negotiations - General [folder 1 of 10], 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Negotiations - General [folder 2 of 10], 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Negotiations - General [folder 3 of 10], 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Negotiations - General [folder 4 of 10], 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Negotiations - General [folder 5 of 10], 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Negotiations - General [folder 6 of 10], 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Negotiations - General [folder 7 of 10], 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Negotiations - General [folder 8 of 10], 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Negotiations - General [folder 9 of 10], 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Negotiations - General [folder 10 of 10], 1966-1970 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Contributions - Food, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Contributions - Money - Individuals, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Contributions - Organizations, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Contributions - Unions, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Messages from unions, organizations, and individuals, 1959-1962 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Messages - Doctor's, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Strike Material - First Seven Hospitals, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Personal Service Registration Forms During Strike, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Strike - Seven Hospitals - April, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Strike - Citizens' Committee for Just Settlement of Strike, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Strike - Assistance, Food, Financial, Welfare, etc., 1959 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Strike - Conduct of Strike at Headquarters, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Strike - Settlement, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Strike - Court Cases, Arbitration, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Strike - Correspondence, Out-of-Town Hospitals, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Strike - Brochures, Leaflets, etc., 1959-1962 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Strike - Ten Hospitals - May, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Strike Material - Hospital Division, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Committee for Justice to Hospital Workers & Prayer Pilgrimage, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- "Vintage of Charity" - Citizen's Committee for Equal Rights, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Strike Assistance - Beth-El & Manhattan, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Beth-El - Publicity, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Flower and Fifth Avenue Hospital Strike, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Strike - Special Letters for Help, Thanks, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Strikes - Miscellaneous Publications [folder 1 of 2], 1958-1959 (Box 49, Folder 5)